<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' standalone='yes' ?>
<CATEGORIES>
	<MUSIC>
		<M1>
			What are humans audibility limits?
		</M1>
		<M2>
			What is the longest title of a movie song?
		</M2>
		<M3>
			What title has the longest song of the world?
		</M3>
		<M4>
			Who built the first violin?
		</M4>
		<M5>
			How many keys does a typical modern piano have?
		</M5>
	</MUSIC>
	<ANIMAL>
		<M1>
			How many hearts does octopus have?
		</M1>
		<M2>
			 What is the longevity of a ladybug?
		</M2>
		<M3>
			What is the name of the biggest land mammal living ever?
		</M3>
		<M4>
			What is the name of the bird able to fly backwards?
		</M4>
		<M5>
			Do animals have different blood types?
		</M5>
	</ANIMAL>
	<NATURE>
		<M1>
			What is the average length and diameter of the ordinary lightning?
		</M1>
		<M2>
			How many potentially inactive volcanoes is located in Alaska?
		</M2>
		<M3>
			What is the oldest tree in the world?
		</M3>
		<M4>
			 Is peanut a nut?
		</M4>
		<M5>
			 What causes a double rainbow?
		</M5>
	</NATURE>
	<SPACE>
		<M1>
			Who set up a camera showing the first step of a man on the moon?
		</M1>
		<M2>
			Where does the cosmos begin officially?
		</M2>
		<M3>
			Why is the skye blue?
		</M3>
		<M4>
			Which planet has the biggest amount of moons and how many?
		</M4>
		<M5>
			What was the name of the first woman who flew into space?
		</M5>
	</SPACE>
	<FILMS>
		<M1>
			Which place did Charlie Chaplin got in the competition for his own double?
		</M1>
		<M2>
			 What was the name of the first movie?
		</M2>
		<M3>
			How much did it cost to produce the world's most expensive film? What's the title?
		</M3>
		<M4>
			Which year was Yoda born?
		</M4>
		<M5>
			Where is the biggest screen movie in the world?
		</M5>
	</FILMS>
	<RANDOM>
		<M1>
			What is the name of the lightest material on earth?
		</M1>
		<M2>
			 How many people in the world know Coca Cola's recipe?
		</M2>
		<M3>
			How long was the longest confirmed hiccup?
		</M3>
		<M4>
			What library has the most books?
		</M4>
		<M5>
			How many rooms are there in the White House?
		</M5>
	</RANDOM>
    <SPORT>
        <M1>
            What is the name of the only sport played on Moon?
        </M1>
        <M2>
            Who was the first woman to win a gold medal in the Olympics?

        </M2>
        <M3>
            How long did the longest Olympic Games last?
        </M3>
        <M4>
            What is the purpose of the golf ball dimples?

        </M4>
        <M5>
            How many people can the largest football stadium in the world store?
        </M5>
    </SPORT>
    <FAMOUS>
        <M1>
            Under what circumstances did Alfred Nobel establish the Nobel Prize?

        </M1>
        <M2>
            What was Elvis Presley doing for living before becoming a singer?
        </M2>
        <M3>
            At what age did Albert Einstein start reading?
        </M3>
        <M4>
            How many paintings did Vincent Van Gogh sold during his life?
        </M4>
        <M5>
            What was the real name of Freddie Mercury?
        </M5>
    </FAMOUS>
    <FOOD>
        <M1>
            What vegetable was carved before pumpkins?

        </M1>
        <M2>
            Why lemon is so sour?
        </M2>
        <M3>
            What thing makes salmon meat pink?
        </M3>
        <M4>
            What was the name of first fast-food restaurant?
        </M4>
        <M5>
            How much is the most expensive coffee in the world?
        </M5>
    </FOOD>
</CATEGORIES>